<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cockatrice_carddatabase version="4">
  <sets>
    <set>
      <name>KKC</name>
      <longname>Kingkiller Chronicles</longname>
      <settype></settype>
    </set>
  </sets>
  <cards>

    <card>
      <name>Kvothe, The Bloodless</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>WURG</colors>
        <manacost>1G</manacost>
        <cmc>2</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Bard Wizard </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/2</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>
LEVEL 1
3/3

LEVEL 2
4/5
</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Auri, Knower of Everything</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>WU</colors>
        <manacost>1WU</manacost>
        <cmc>3</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Human Wizard </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/2</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>Spells you cast have “Gift a card” and “If the gift was promised, add one mana of any color.”. (You may promise an opponent a gift as you cast this spell. If you do, when it enters, they draw a card.)
Whenever you give a gift, you may promise it to yourself and an opponent. If you do, the opponent gets the gift first.
If Auri would be dealt damage, she phases out instead.</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Denna, The Nameless</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>R</colors>
        <manacost>RR</manacost>
        <cmc>2</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Human Bard </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/3</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>Vanishing 2, Haste, Skulk (This creature enters with two time counters on it. At the beginning of your upkeep, remove a time counter from it. When the last is removed, sacrifice it. This creature can’t be blocked by creatures with greater power.)
When Denna, The Nameless enters, create a Treasure token, draw a card, and explore.</text>
      <related count="1">Treasure</related>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Kote, The Inkeeper</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>WURG</colors>
        <manacost>2R/GW/U</manacost>
        <cmc>4</cmc>
        <type>Creature - Human  </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>3/4</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>Deathtouch, Trample
When Kote, The Inkeeper leaves the battlefield, exile all permanents with mana value four or greater.</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Ctheah, The Infinite Sight</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>URG</colors>
        <manacost>GUR</manacost>
        <cmc>3</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Faerie Demon </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>0/4</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>Defender, Indestructible
Whenever a creature deals damage to Ctheah, The Infinite Sight, gain control of it until your next endstep.
On your endstep, exile target creature you control and return it to the battlefield under your control.</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Elorin, The Namer</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>WUR</colors>
        <manacost>URW</manacost>
        <cmc>3</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Human Wizard </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>3/3</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>On your upkeep, put a charge counter on Elorin.
{5}: X is equal to the number of charge counters on Elorin. Exile Elorin. Choose one —
• Choose up to X permanents. The chosen permanents lose all types and abilities, becoming enchantments named “Stone”.
• Choose up to XX permanents. Return the chosen permanents to their owner’s hands.
• Deal XXX damage split among any number of targets.</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Bast, The Prince of Twilight</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>RG</colors>
        <manacost>2RG</manacost>
        <cmc>4</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Faerie Noble </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>2/2</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>When Bast, The Prince of Twilight or another legendary creature enters the battlefield under your control, put two +1/+1 counters on Bast and deal 2 damage to target opponent.
Whenever Bast attacks, you may search your library for a basic land card, put it onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle.
1G: Bast gains trample until end of turn.</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Broken Bindings</name>
      <set rarity="rare">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>WU</colors>
        <manacost>WUU</manacost>
        <cmc>3</cmc>
        <type>Instant</type>
        <maintype>Instant</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>3</tablerow>
      <text>Gift a Food (You may promise an opponent a gift as you cast this spell. If you do, they create a Food token before its other effects. It’s an artifact with “{2}, {T}, Sacrifice this artifact: You gain 3 life.”)
If the gift was promised, this spell has split second. (As long as this spell is on the stack, players can’t cast spells or activate abilities that aren’t mana abilities.)
Target player loses 2 life for each spell they control. Counter all spells controlled by them.</text>
      <related count="1">Food</related>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Burst of Innovation</name>
      <set rarity="rare">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>RG</colors>
        <manacost>1RG</manacost>
        <cmc>3</cmc>
        <type>Sorcery</type>
        <maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>3</tablerow>
      <text>Gift a Clue. (You may promise an opponent a gift as you cast this spell. If you do, they create a Clue token before its other effects. It’s an artifact with “{2}, {T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a Card.”)
Create two Treasure tokens and a Food token. If the gift was promised, instead create a Powerstone token and a Food token. (It’s an artifact with “{T}: Add {C}. This mana can’t be spent to cast a nonartifact spell.”)</text>
      <related count="1">Clue</related>
      <related count="2">Treasure</related>
      <related count="1">Powerstone</related>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Shaed</name>
      <set rarity="uncommon">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <manacost>3</manacost>
        <cmc>3</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Artifact - Equipment </type>
        <maintype>Artifact</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>Equipped creature can’t be blocked and has hexproof.
Equip – Pay 2 life</text>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Devi, The Exiled</name>
      <set rarity="mythic">KKC</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>WR</colors>
        <manacost>2RW</manacost>
        <cmc>4</cmc>
        <type>Legendary Creature - Human Wizard </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/3</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>Gift a Treasure
Whenever an opponent sacrifices a Treasure, you gain 2 life.
When Devi enters, if the gift was promised, create a Powerstone token.
Whenever a player casts an artifact spell, you and target opponent create a Treasure token.</text>
      <related count="1">Treasure</related>
      <related count="1">Powerstone</related>
    </card>

    <!-->Tokens</-->


  </cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>